tractorsupply.com 2019-12-03

# Tractor Supply Co. Privacy Policy

  1. Our Customer Pledge
  2. Use of Cookies
  3. Collection and Use of Personal Information
  4. Sharing Information With Third Parties
  5. Information You Submit Publicly
  6. Interest-Based Advertising
  7. Third Party Links and Data
  8. Transfer of Information to the United States
  9. What Should Parents Know About Children
  10. Security
  11. How Long Is My Personal Information Retained
  12. Updating Your Information and Choices
  13. Changes to the Privacy Policy
  14. Access to Personal Information
  15. California Privacy Rights
  16. Security Questions or Comments
  17. How to Contact Tractor Supply
  18. Changes to the Privacy and Security Statement

Effective Date:  September 19, 2018

**Introduction and Overview**

You have arrived at a web site that is provided by Tractor Supply Company and/or its affiliated and subsidiary companies (collectively "Tractor Supply").  This Privacy Policy governs your use of www.tractorsupply.com and any other official Tractor Supply sites, including mobile sites or apps, and any interactive features, applications, and/or services that we make available through a site or interactive platform that posts a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively referred to as the “Site”).  This Privacy Policy also applies to Personal Information (defined below) that we may collect from you in our Tractor Supply retail stores (“Store” or “Stores”), through any Tractor Supply Customer Call Center, and through official surveys and sweepstakes entry forms, or in any other instance when you contact us. 

We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe what information Tractor Supply collects from you, why we collect it, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share it with third parties, and otherwise manage the personal information you provide to us. 

This Privacy Policy also describes the choices you can make about how we use your information.  To the extent we provide you notice on our Site or in our Stores of different of additional privacy policies or practices (e.g., at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use.

Tractor Supply does engage third party service providers ("Service Providers") with whom your information may be shared. Service Providers have their own security policies and Tractor Supply is not responsible for their conduct. Unless explicitly stated otherwise, any current, updated and new products and services shall be subject to this Privacy Policy.  By using the services provided at the Stores or the Customer Call Centers or by using the Site, you agree to all of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Tractor Supply cares about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please contact us at <https://www.tractorsupply.com/tsc/customer-solutions>

**1\. Our Customer Pledge**

Tractor Supply will collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**A. Collection and Use of Information You Provide To Us.**

We may ask you to provide us: (1) your first and last name, email address, home address, phone number, driver’s license number, credit and debit card numbers, checking account numbers, date of birth and social security number (when applying for or requesting services related to the Tractor Supply Credit Card) or other information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally (hereinafter “Personal Information”); and/or (2) demographic information, such as your zip code (“Demographic Information”). We may collect this information from you such as when you:

  * Purchase, order, return, exchange or request certain information about Tractor Supply's products and services;
  * Sign up to add, view and/or apply tax exemptions associated with your account;
  * Request warranty or tax exempt information,;
  * Sign up to join the Tractor Supply online mailing list;
  * Sign up to receive the Tractor Supply Newsletter;
  * Enroll in the Neighbor’s Club Rewards Program;
  * Participate in Tractor Supply’s buy online/ pick up in store program;
  * Utilize features of a Tractor Supply in store Kiosk;
  * Contact a Customer Call Center or customer service desk;
  * Visit, create a customer account or place an order through the Replacement Parts Portal;
  * Apply for a Tractor Supply Credit Card;
  * Visit, register on, or participate in the features of one of Tractor Supply's Sites, such as a bulletin board or community;
  * Enter into a contest or sweepstakes or respond to one of Tractor Supply's surveys;
  * Provide Tractor Supply with comments or suggestions;
  * Submit an application for employment;
  * Provide Tractor Supply with any information contributed to our Sites on your behalf; and
  * Provide Tractor Supply other contact information.

Your decision to provide this information is voluntary, but if you choose not to provide this requested information you may not be able to take advantage of all of the sites features or our services.

**B. Information collected when you use the Site.**

In addition to the information you choose to submit to us, we and/or our service providers may automatically collect and/or store certain non- personally identifiable information when you visit or interact with the Site, including in store kiosks, or communicate with us by email (“Usage Information’).  This Usage Information may be stored and/or accessed from your personal computer, laptop, tablet, mobile phone or other device (a ‘Device”) whenever you visit or interact with our Site or communicate with us by email. 

  * Usage Information may include but is not limited to:
  * Your IP address or other unique identifier (“Device Identifier”);
  * Your Device browser, operating system, and mobile network information;
  * The areas within our Site that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you and your preferences;
  * Your general location; and
  * Certain other Device data, including the time of day you visit the Site, among other information.

We may use various methods to collect and/or store Usage Information, such as:

_(i) General Tracking Information.   _Tractor Supply keeps records of the pages visited by each site user. Tractor Supply aggregates this information with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. Tractor Supply uses this information to improve its Site and to develop functions and user tools which will make it more responsive to the needs and preferences of Tractor Supply customers.

_(ii) Cookies.   _The Site uses a technology called "cookies" to help facilitate transactions on the Site. A cookie is an element of software code that Tractor Supply Sites can send to your browser, which is then stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. All pages on our Sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. If you have registered with our Sites, these cookies: (1) may let us know who you are; (2) are necessary to access the personal information previously provided to us by you in order to deliver products and personalized services; and (3) will provide us and our Service Providers with information that we will use to personalize our Sites in accordance with your preferences. Should you decide not to accept cookies from our Sites, you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our Site.

_(iii) Tracer Tags._ Tractor Supply's Sites may use a technology called "tracer tags", which may also be referred to as "Clear GIFs" or "Web Beacons". This technology allows us to identify which pages you visit on our Sites. These tags are used by us to help optimize and update our Sites for you and other future website visitors.

_(iv) Browser Do Not Track Signals.   _Although our websites currently do not have a mechanism to recognize the various web browser Do Not Track signals, we do offer our customers choices to manage their preferences by referencing the "How to Contact Tractor Supply" Section (Section 16) of this Privacy and Security Statement.

_(v) Other Information.   _We may collect additional automatic information about your visit to our Site, such as time of day, browser type and version, browser language, your operating system and platform, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet. This information is used for analytical purposes and to help us provide services to our customers. We may also use this information to administer and troubleshoot our Sites.

_(vi) Aggregate Information._   On occasion we may provide this aggregate information (which shall not include personally identifiable information) to vendors, investors, potential advertisers, or news agencies to demonstrate the amount of interest in our Site and to help us plan for technical infrastructure requirements.

These technologies (or ones we incorporate in the future) are used for a variety of purposes, including:

  * Prevention of fraudulent activity and improved security functionality.
  * To administer and assess the performance of the Site.
  * To analyze customer trends.
  * To offer you enhanced functionality when accessing the Site, including identifying you when you sign-in to our Site or keeping track of your specified preferences.
  * To deliver content relevant to your interests on our Site and third-party sites based upon how you interact with our advertisements and/or content.
  * To track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

 Tractor Supply will not use Usage Information collected to market directly to that person.  Usage Information may; however, be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to Users in the aggregate.

**C.  Location-Based Information**

Our Site may use location-based services to verify your location, deliver you relevant content and/or advertising based on your location, as well as to share your location with our service providers as part of the location-based services we offer. Further, we or our Service Providers may use your location information to display our nearest Store location to you. You have the ability to turn location-based services on and off by adjusting the settings of your Internet browser or mobile device.

**D.  Information We Collect From Third Parties**

We may also receive information about you from your friends and other third parties, and combine or link that information with information we have about you. To the extent we combine information we receive from third parties with your Personal Information, the combined information, unless disclosed otherwise, will be treated as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. In no other circumstances will this Privacy Policy apply to information we receive about you from third parties.

**E.  Information We Collect When You Interact with Third-Party Sites.**

The Site may allow certain kinds of interactions between the Site and your account on a third-party site or application. The use of this functionality may involve the third-party site providing information, including Personal Information, to us. For example, when you register with the Site, you may have an option to use your Facebook account to facilitate the registration or transaction process on the Site. If you choose to use this functionality, the third-party site may send Personal Information about you to us. If so, we will treat this information as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. In addition, we may provide links on the Site to facilitate sending a communication from the Site. For example, we may use third parties to facilitate emails, Tweets or Facebook postings. These third parties may retain any information used or provided in any such communications or activities and these third parties’ practices are not subject to our Privacy Policy. You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such tools.

**F.  Information You Provide About a Third Party**

You may send someone else a communication from the Site, such as sending an invitation to a friend. If so, the information you provide (names, email addresses, mobile number, etc.) will be used to facilitate the communication and will not be used for marketing purposes unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on our Site, your email address, mobile number, name or username and message may be included in the communication sent to your addressee(s). Some of these tools may be third-party tools subject to third-party privacy policies.

You may also provide information about a third party to the extent you have authorized that person to pick up products that you have purchased online.  The information you provide (names, email addresses, mobile number, etc.) will only be used to facilitate product pick-up and will not be used for marketing purposes unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise.  NOTE THAT YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY AND ALL ITEMS PURCHASED ONLINE AND PICKED UP BY A DESIGNATED THIRD PARTY. Unless and until we receive a third party’s written consent, we will not use any information you provide about a third party to contact that person for any reason, including reasons related to the pick-up of products purchased by you on our Site.      

**2\. How we use the information we collect.**

We may use your Personal Information, Demographic Information or Usage Information for a variety of business purposes, including, but not limited to the following:

  * Improving the effectiveness of our Site, marketing endeavors and service offerings;
  * Processing credit applications and transactions;
  * Neighbor’s Club Account administration;
  * Site registration;
  * Processing and completing purchases, returns and similar transactions;
  * Providing customer service, including managing warranty claims;
  * Managing Replacement Parts Portal accounts and transactions;
  * Notifying you of product recalls or providing other information concerning products you have purchased;
  * Sending you direct mail offerings;
  * Sending you email communications such as electronic newsletters about our products, services and promotions;
  * Sending you email about orders you have made on the Site, in the Store or via the Customer Call center. 
  * Enabling you to participate in the Site’s features such as surveys and promotions;
  * Identifying your product and service preferences and informing you of new or additional products, services and promotions that may be of interest to you;
  * Providing mobile marketing messages and service messages;
  * Evaluating employment inquiries or applications;
  * For internal business purposes;
  * To enforce our terms of use and policies;
  * To respond to legal requests and prevent legal harm; and
  * For purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**3\. Sharing Information With Third Parties**

**A.  When You Request We Share With Third Parties.**

We may share information with third parties at your request. In the event we do so, all information we disclose will be subject to the privacy policies and practices of such third parties. In addition, the third parties may store, collect or otherwise have access to your information when you interact with their technologies, content or apps on our Site or link to them from our Site. This may include using third-party tools such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest or other third-party posting or content sharing tools. We are not responsible for the practices of such third parties and, therefore, you should review such third-party privacy policies prior to interacting with them.

**B.  Third Parties Providing Services to Tractor Supply.**

We may use third party service providers to perform certain services, such as: (a) to assist us in e-commerce operations; (b) to manage a database of customer information; (c) hosting the Site; (d) designing and/or operating the Site’s features; (e) tracking the Site’s activities and analytics; (f) enabling us to send you special offers or perform other administrative services; (g) to allow you to participate in live chat on the Site; and (h) other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. We may provide third parties with access to your information to carry out the services they are performing for us. Third-party analytics and other service providers such as Google Analytics may set and access their own technologies on your Device and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you. These service providers use the technology described above to help us analyze how users use the Site. We are not responsible for those third party technologies or activities arising out of them. However, some third parties may offer you certain choices regarding their practices. For example, to learn about opting out of Google Analytics, please click here. To learn about opting out of the use of Adobe cookies for analytics and on-site personalization, please click here. We are not responsible for the effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties’ opt-out options.

**C.  Service Providers.**

Some of our operations, such as our Customer Call Centers, may be managed by unaffiliated companies. These companies may have access to your personal information on a confidential basis only to the extent necessary to perform their functions.

**D. Shipping.**

If your purchases are being shipped to you, we will share your shipping information with our delivery Service Providers (United Parcel Service, FedEx, U.S. Postal Service, or other delivery companies we select).

**E.  To Protect the Rights of Tractor Supply and our Users.**

We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that doing so is necessary or appropriate to: (i) protect or defend the rights, safety or property of Tractor Supply or third parties (including through the enforcement of this Policy, our Terms of Use, and other applicable agreements and policies); or (ii) comply with legal and regulatory obligations (e.g., pursuant to law enforcement inquiries, subpoenas or court orders).

**F. Affiliates and Business Transfer.**

We may share your information with our parent, subsidiaries and affiliates. We also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all such information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Site and/or our Stores; or (ii) in connection with a merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our interests and/or assets or other corporate change, including during the course of any due diligence process.

**G.** **Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions.**

We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (any, a “Promotion”) through the Site, in the Stores or through one of our social media pages that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, allowing the sponsor of the Promotion to use your name, voice and likeness in advertising associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion’s official rules, such as on a winner’s list.

**H. Co-Branded Areas.**

Certain areas of the Site may be provided to you in association with third parties (“Co-Branded Areas”) such as co-promotional partners and may require you to disclose Personal Information to them. Such Co-Branded Areas will identify the third party and indicate if they have a privacy policy that applies to their collection and use of your information. If you elect to register for products and/or services, communicate with such third parties or download their content or applications, you may be providing your information to both us and the third party. Further, if you sign-in to a Co-Branded Area with a username and password obtained on the Site, your Personal Information may be disclosed to the identified third parties for that Co-Branded Area. Examples of a Co-Branded Area include:

**Extended Warranty Services.** If you purchase a Tractor Supply Extended Warranty Service, you will be required to provide personal information to a third party.

**Replacement Parts Portal.**   The Replacement Parts Portal is operated by OrderTree, a third party Service Provider.  If you register an account, place an order or provide Personal Information through the Replacement Parts Portal, you will be providing your Personal Information to third party Service Providers. 

**Tractor Supply Credit Card.**   The Tractor Supply Credit card services are administered by a third party.  If you apply for a Tractor Supply Credit Card, you will be required to provide personal information to said third party.

We are not responsible for such third party’s data collection or practices and you should look to such third party privacy policies for more information.

**I. Secure Shopping**

When you place orders on a Site, your order information, including your card number and delivery address, is transmitted through the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology works with your browser to encrypt your order information before transmitting it to our server.

**4\. Information You Submit Publicly**

**A. User Content and Public Information.**

The Site may permit you to submit ideas, photographs, videos, audio recordings, questions, comments, suggestions or other content, including Personal Information (collectively, “User Content”), on blogs, social media sites and message boards and other public forums, as well as in connection with our Site’s product review service and wishlist feature. We or others may store, display, publish, distribute or otherwise use User Content online or offline in any media or format and may or may not attribute the User Content to you. Others may have access to this User Content and may have the ability to share it with third parties. Please note that Tractor Supply Imports does not control who will have access to the information that you choose to make public, and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy or keep it secure. We are not responsible for the privacy or security of any information that you make publicly available on the Site or what others do with information you share with them on the Site.

**B. Name and Likeness.**

We may also publish your name, voice, likeness and other Personal Information that is part of your User Content, and we may use the content, or any portion of the content, for advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. For full terms and conditions regarding User Content you submit, please review our Terms of Use.

**5\. Interest-Based Advertising**

We may use your Personal Data to help us decide which products, services and offers may be of interest to you.

We use third party analytics and social media providers to collect information about your use of the Site, see the overall patterns of usage on the Site, deliver advertisements to your social media account based on email addresses, optimize ad performance, and to determine whether our advertising is effective.  We use analytics tools and other third party technologies, including cookies, to collect Personal Information and Non-Personal Information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our Site.  These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information.

The third party analytics companies (like Google and IBM) who collect information on our Site and other online products and/or sites may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products relating to your activities across their network of websites. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.

In addition to our use of technologies as described herein, we may permit certain third party companies, including online ad networks such as Google and Conversant, to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to you based on your use of our Services and to otherwise collect and use data about your use of our Services. These networks track your online activities over time and across third party websites and online services by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of the technologies described in the “Information We Collect When You Use the Site” Section above, and they use this information to show you advertisements that are tailored to your individual interests.  This collection and ad targeting takes place both on our Site and on third-party websites that participate in the ad network. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

**Opting out of analytics:**   You may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.  Google has additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, and Restrictions.  You may learn more at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. 

**Opting out of Conversant:** You may opt out of Conversant by [clicking here](http://dtmc.tractorsupply.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=62737&cname=Tractor%20Supply&cmagic=175826&clogo=62737.png&loc=us&lang=en-us).

You may view a list of other third party service providers who collect information, and/or opt-out of such collection of information about you, by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. 

Please note that opting out of receiving targeted ads will not prevent you from being served advertisements generally; rather, opting out means that the online ads presented will not be based on your particular interests.

**We currently do not respond to Do Not Track Signals.   **Some third parties, such as companies that offer Internet browsers, have developed signals (e.g., browser do not track signals) that give you a choice regarding the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services. Currently, we do not monitor or take any action with respect to these signals or other mechanisms offered by Internet browsers. If you would like more information on self-regulatory programs that permit you to exercise choice, click on the ad networks link in the paragraph above.

**6\. Third Party Links and Data.**

The Site may contain content that is supplied by a third party, and those third parties may collect Usage Information and your Device Identifier when pages from the Site are served to you. In addition, Tractor Supply's Site may include links to services that are operated and controlled by third parties. Examples include:

  * the Replacement Parts Portal;
  * the Tractor Supply Credit Card;
  * the Power Plus Protection Plan;

We are not responsible for the data collection and privacy practices employed by any of these third parties. For example, if you “click” on a link, the “click” may take you off the Site onto a different site. These other sites may independently collect data about you and may or may not have their own published privacy policies.

The inclusion of any link does not imply Tractor Supply's endorsement of any other company, its websites, or its products and/or services. We have no control over such websites and therefore have no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked websites may collect, use or disclose and otherwise treat your personal information.

Third party Service Providers may need access to some of your personal information. In such cases, we only provide third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We may also provide your information to our affiliated companies and successors. We reserve the right to provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our clients, traffic patterns and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns, but does not contain personally identifiable information about any individual user.

**7\. Transfer of Information to the United States**

Our Site is operated in the United States and Canada and intended for users located only in the United States and Canada. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States. By using the Site or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing and storage of your information in the United States.

**8\. What Should Parents Know About Children**

We understand the importance of protecting children’s privacy in the interactive world. We do not use the Site to knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent. If you are a child under 13 years of age, you are not permitted to use the Site and should not send any information about yourself to us through the Site.

In the event that we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from any child, we will dispose of that information in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child under the age of 13 has provided us with information without your consent, please contact us at customersolutions@tractorsupply.com, and we will take reasonable steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our databases.

**9\. Security**

We incorporate commercially reasonable safeguards to help protect and secure your Personal Information. However, no data transmission over the Internet, mobile networks, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our Site, and you provide us with your information at your own risk.

**10\. How Long Is My Personal Information Retained**

We will keep your Personal Information only as long as is commercially reasonable for the purposes described in the Privacy Policy or for any such period as may be required by applicable law.

**11\. Updating Your Information and Choices**

You may update or correct information about you through the Site’s account registration forms or by contacting us:

  1. Send an e-mail to: customersolutions@tractorsupply.com
  2. Call 1-877-718-6750;
  3. Send your request by mail to:

Tractor Supply Company  
5401 Virginia Way  
Brentwood, TN 37027  
ATTN: Internet Customer Service

  4. Fill out a comment form online now. [Click here to go to Contact Us comment form](https://www.tractorsupply.com/tsc/customer-solutions).

You may opt out of receiving promotional mail, emails and/or text messages from us by sending an email to customersolutions@tractorsupply.com or letter to Tractor Supply Company, 5401 Virginia Way, Brentwood, TN 37027, ATTN: Internet Customer Service.  Please be sure to include your current information and the requested changes you would like us to make to your marketing profile in your communication. You may also cancel or modify our email marketing communications you receive from us by following the instructions contained within our promotional emails.

Additionally, if you subscribe to text messages from us, you can terminate a particular text message subscription by reply texting “TSCSTOP.” Please allow 10 days to process your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Tractor Supply. 

Please note that we will retain your information for legitimate business purposes or as required by law. Also, if you have made any public postings on the Site such as in user comment sections of the Site, these communications cannot generally be removed.

Please note that we may still send you certain communications relating to your account or use of our Site, such as administrative and service announcements and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you choose to opt-out from receiving our marketing communications.

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, or practices described in it, please direct your communication to the above email and/or address.

**12\. Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy and your use of our Site indicates your consent to the privacy policy posted at the time of use and you will be bound by such changes unless you advise us in writing, by phone or by e-mail that you wish to withdraw your consent (as per the procedure outlined above). You are responsible for regularly reviewing the Privacy Policy and any changes thereto.

**13\. Access to Personal Information**

As a registered user with our Sites, you can access your profile information at any time by:

  * Clicking on the "Sign In" (link) button at the top of any page on the Sites on which you registered, then
  * Clicking on the "Your Account" (link) button on the page header or on the "Your Account" link under Customer Support.

For further instructions on accessing the personal information that Tractor Supply may have about you, please see the "How to Contact Tractor Supply" Section 16 of this Privacy Policy.

**14\. California Privacy Rights**

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by Tractor Supply pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact us.

**15\. Security Questions or Comments**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns, please contact us in any one of the ways identified in Section 16.

**16\. How to Contact Tractor Supply.**

You may contact us in one of the following ways:

  1. Send an e-mail to: customersolutions@tractorsupply.com
  2. Call 1-877-718-6750;
  3. Send your request by mail to:

Tractor Supply Company  
5401 Virginia Way  
Brentwood, TN 37027  
ATTN: Internet Customer Service

  4. Fill out a comment form online now. [Click here to go to Contact Us comment form](https://www.tractorsupply.com/tsc/customer-solutions).

**17\. Changes to the Privacy and Security Statement**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion. Any updates to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Continued use of our Sites, Stores, Customer Call Centers or other Tractor Supply services following our posting of the change notice or an updated Privacy Policy will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.
